<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://www.adrianmoreno.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.adrianmoreno.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building A Personal Website with GitHub Pages, Domain, and Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.adrianmoreno.info/blog/personalwebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.adrianmoreno.info/blog/personalwebsite/</guid>
      <description>Building a personal website can be a rewarding project, providing a platform to showcase your work, share your thoughts, and create an online presence. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through my journey of building a personal website using GitHub Pages, purchasing a domain from Alibaba, and utilizing the Hugo framework.&#xA;Step 1: Setting Up GitHub Pages GitHub Pages is a fantastic service for hosting websites directly from a GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Year Project</title>
      <link>https://www.adrianmoreno.info/experience/graduatedesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.adrianmoreno.info/experience/graduatedesign/</guid>
      <description>Concurrent Runtime for Pat Language My final year project focused on tackling the complexities of concurrent programming, such as thread deadlocks and communication mismatches.&#xA;Building upon the foundation of the Pat language created by my supervisor, I developed a concurrent runtime for Pat. Pat introduces a mailbox type system and concurrent programming primitives to tightly constrain concurrent tasks and communication flows.&#xA;Although Pat had an existing type checker, it lacked a runtime interpreter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intern - StarDust Project</title>
      <link>https://www.adrianmoreno.info/experience/stardust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.adrianmoreno.info/experience/stardust/</guid>
      <description>First intern as developer During my summer internship with the StarDust team at the University of Glasgow, I worked on a groundbreaking project involving Pat, the first programming language to implement mailbox type checking. The project entailed designing a &amp;ldquo;mailboxer&amp;rdquo; to convert Erlang code into Pat for type checking and then convert it back.&#xA;My responsibilities included identifying and resolving bugs within the &amp;ldquo;mailboxer&amp;rdquo; and enhancing Pat&amp;rsquo;s error reporting system by adding precise error position and source code display features.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
